Railway Labor Executives' Association Records 5484
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series X: Office Files, 1967
  - Government: R.S. and I. Cases - Approval of Changes in Signal Installations (File 2) [folder 3 of 3], 1967 (Box 136, Folder 57c)
  - Government: R.S. and I. Cases - Approval of Changes in Signal Installations (File 3), 1967 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Government: Boston and Main - BS Ap. 14827 - ICC (Interstate Commerce Commission) Number 28000, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Government: Bureau of Transportation Economics and Statistics, General, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Government: Rules for Reporting of Wages and Hours, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Government: Railroad Service Board, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Government: Complaints regarding Administration of Safety Laws and Regulations, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Government: Bureau of Locomotive Inspection - General, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Government: Power Brakes, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission Safety Dockets, General, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Government: Prevention of Railway-Highway Grade Crossing Accidents [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 137, Folder 10a)
  - Government: Prevention of Railway-Highway Grade Crossing Accidents [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 137, Folder 10b)
  - Government: Union Tank Car Company Docket Number 32258, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Government: Application of Safety Appliance Acts to Track Motor Cars Number 32248, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Government: Annual Report of Railroad Accidents Reported Under General Order Number 22-B 1, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 13)
    Report for accidents in 1966.
  - Government: Motor Carriers, General, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, General, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Membership and Staff Appointments, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Less than Carload Discontinuances, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Rules of Procedure and Administration, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 18)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Amendments regarding Individuals as Bargaining Agents, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 19)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Appropriations, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 20)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Lists of Carriers and Designated Officers to Handle Disputes, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 21)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Monthly Reports on Status of Cases, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 22)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Decisions and Certifications [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 137, Folder 23a)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Decisions and Certifications [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 137, Folder 23b)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Flight Engineers' Representation Case, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 24)
  - Government: National Railroad Adjustment Board, General, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 25)
  - Government: NRAB First Division, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 26)
  - Government: NRAB Second Division, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 27)
  - Government: NRAB Third Division, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 28)
  - Government: NRAB Fourth Division, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 29)
  - Government: NRAB Organizations Qualified to Participate in Selection of Members, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 30)
  - Government: NRAB Membership, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 31)
  - Government: NRAB Application of Awards, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 32)
  - Government: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen vs. Monon Railroad National Mediation Board (NMB C. 3196), 1967 (Box 137, Folder 33)
  - Government: NRAB, Awards Adopting Gunther Decision, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 34)
  - Government: National Railroad Adjustment Board - Third Party Notices, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 35)
  - Government: Grade Crossing Reference, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 36)
    Agenda item 1.3/6
  - Legislation: Interstate Commerce Act [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 138, Folder 1a)
  - Legislation: Interstate Commerce Act [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 138, Folder 1b)
  - Legislation: Report of Proceedings, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Hearing held before the Subcommittee on Transportation and Aeronautics, Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce. H.R. 7004, H.R. 260, and H.R. 519. Volume 2. April 26, 1967
  - Legislation: Letter to Senate Commerce Committee and responses regarding passenger train discussion, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    November 1, 1967
  - Legislation: Letter to members of Senate Commerce Committee and House Interstate and Foreign Commerce and responses regarding Passenger Train Discussion, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    November 8, 1967
  - Legislation: Letter to all members of Congress and responses regarding rail passenger service, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    September 14, 1967
  - Legislation: Passenger Train Services - Discussion [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 138, Folder 6a)
  - Legislation: Passenger Train Services - Discussion [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 138, Folder 6b)
  - Legislation: Supplemental Material, Passenger Train Services - Discussion, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Pell Plan, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Car and Track Inspection Bill, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Highway Financing Trust Fund, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: Repeal of Taxes on Transportation of Persons, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: National Transportation Policy - High Speed Ground Transportation, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: Repeal of Section 13a of Interstate Commerce Act, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: Minimum Rate Exemption Amendments, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: National Railroad Freight Car Supply Bill, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: Interstate Commerce Act (I.C.A.) - Freight Forwarder Bill, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: S. 1719 - State Income Tax Law, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: Supplemental Material for the Railroad Retirement Act, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: Railroad Retirement Act [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 138, Folder 19a)
  - Legislation: Railroad Retirement Act [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 138, Folder 19b)
  - Legislation: Bill to Amend Railroad Retirement Act [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 138, Folder 20a)
    Includes letters from Board
  - Legislation: Bill to Amend Railroad Retirement Act [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 138, Folder 20b)
  - Legislation: "Super Grades" H.R. 7377 and S. 1732 (1961), 1967 (Box 138, Folder 21)
  - Legislation: 1961 Amendments - H.R. 8597 and S. 2395, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 22)
  - Legislation: Railroad Pension Conference Postcards regarding Amending Railroad Retirement Act, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 23)
  - Legislation: Supplemental Pensions, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 24)
  - Legislation: Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 25)
  - Legislation: Railroad Unemployment Insurance Situation - General, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 26)
  - Legislation: Labor-Management Relations Act, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 27)
  - Legislation: Social Security Act, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 28)
  - Legislation: Correspondence in answer to telegram of December 13 regarding Social Security Bill, 1967-1968 (Box 138, Folder 29)
  - Legislation: Medical Benefits to Retired Persons (MEDICARE), 1967 (Box 138, Folder 30)
  - Legislation: Mail, Parcel Post, and Express [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 138, Folder 31a)
  - Legislation: Mail, Parcel Post, and Express [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 138, Folder 31b)
  - Legislation: Letters and Telegrams from Congress regarding letter of November 27 and telegram of November 29 regarding H.R. 7977, 1967-1968 (Box 138, Folder 32)
  - Legislation: State Legislation, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 33)
  - Legislation: Full Crew Laws, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 34)
  - Legislation: Right-to-Work Laws (States), 1967 (Box 138, Folder 35)
  - Legislation: State Public Utilities Commissions, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 36)
  - Legislation: Coal Slurry Pipeline Legislation, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 37)
  - Legislation: Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 38)
  - Legislation: Letters from Congress regarding H.R. 100 (situs picketing bill) [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 138, Folder 39a)
  - Legislation: Letters from Congress regarding H.R. 100 (situs picketing bill) [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 138, Folder 39b)
  - Legislation: National Labor Relations Act (Right to Work 13b), 1967 (Box 138, Folder 40)
  - Legislation: Mass Transportation Act (Legislation Passed in 1964), 1967 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: American Municipal Association (Mass Transit), 1967 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Bills Pertaining to Federal Employees and Veterans, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Waterways, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Anti-Labor Legislation, General, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: Canadian Anti-Labor Legislation, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: PL 89-236 (Migratory Farm Labor) Canadian Situation, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Depressed Areas, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Minimum Wage Legislation, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Hours of Service Law Amendments, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: Clayton Act Amendments, Rail Mergers Moratorium, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: Congressional Investigation of Railroads' Financial Condition, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: Conservation Legislation-Interior Department, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: S. Res. 102, Settlement of Railroad Work Rules Dispute, PL 88-108, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: Antitrust and Monopoly Subcommittee Hearings on Economic Concentration, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: Railroad Safety Legislation, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 16a)
  - Legislation: Miscellaneous Senator Correspondence, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 16b)
  - Legislation: RLEA Legislative Program (90th Congress), 1967 (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: Railroad Taxes, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: Department of Transportation [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 139, Folder 19a)
  - Legislation: Senator Correspondence Regarding Receipt of Informational Pamphlets, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 19b)
  - Legislation: Department of Transportation, Alaska Railroad, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: Bank Holding Company Act Amendment (FEC), 1967 (Box 139, Folder 21)
  - Legislation: Department of Transportation Appropriations, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 22)
  - Legislation: Surcharge Tax Proposal, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 23)
  - Legislation: Legislative Reorganization Act, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 24a)
  - Legislation: Proceedings Under Section 13a of the Interstate Commerce Act, 1966 (Box 139, Folder 24b)
  - Legislation: Congressional Quarterly - Weekly Report, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 24c)
    For December 15, 1967 and September 29, 1967.
  - Legislation: Supplements to Congressional Data Book, 1965-1966 (Box 139, Folder 24d)
  - Legislation: Congressional Quarterly - Legislators and Lobbyists, 1966 (Box 139, Folder 24e)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, General, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Selected National and Railroad Data [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 140, Folder 2a)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Selected National and Railroad Data [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 140, Folder 2b)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Membership and Staff Appointments, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Administrative Practices and Procedures, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Field Offices, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Mechanizations and Centralization of Claims Payment, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Coverage of Railroads and Unions as Employers, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Status of Funds, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, PRC's Impact on Railroad Retirement and Unemployment Insurance System, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Military Service Credits, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Educational Program, Meetings, Films, Etc., 1967 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Press Releases, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Supplement Retirement Plans, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Monongahela Connecting Railroad Company Transcript, Supplementary Pensions, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Safety Studies, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 15)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, National Reporting Officers' Memoranda, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 16)
  - Government: Administration of Medicare, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 17)
  - Government: US Information Agency, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 18)
  - Government: President's Committee on the Physically Handicapped, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 19)
  - Government: Presidential Appointment of Operating Employees' Commission, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 20)
  - Government: President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 21)
  - Government: Peace Corps, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 22)
  - Government: President's Commission on the Status of Women, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 23)
  - Government: Freedom from Hunger Foundation, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 24)
  - Government: White House Conference on "To Fulfill These Rights", 1967 (Box 140, Folder 25)
  - Government: Federal Housing Administration, 221(d)(3) Plan, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 26)
  - Judicial: Court Cases, General [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 140, Folder 27a)
  - Judicial: Court Cases, General [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 140, Folder 27b)
  - Judicial: Union Shop Case (Street-Duckworth-Looper), 1967 (Box 140, Folder 28)
  - RLEA: General, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 29)
  - RLEA: Emergency Relief Fund, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 30)
  - RLEA: Constitution and By-Laws, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 31)
  - RLEA: Officers and Members, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 32)
  - RLEA: American Railway Supervisors Association, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 33)
  - RLEA: American Train Dispatchers Association, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 34)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 35)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 36)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 37)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 38)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 39)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 40)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Railway Clerks, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 41)
  - RLEA: BRC-UAL, Youngdahl Decision, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 42)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 43)
  - RLEA: International Association of Machinists, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 44)
  - RLEA: International Brotherhood of Boilermakers and Blacksmiths, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 45)
  - RLEA: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 46)
  - RLEA: International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 47)
  - RLEA: International Organization Masters, Mates, and Pilots of America, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 48)
  - RLEA: National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 49)
  - RLEA: Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 50)
  - RLEA: Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 51)
  - RLEA: Railway Employees' Department, AFL-CIO, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 52)
  - RLEA: Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 53)
  - RLEA: Switchmen's Union of North America, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 54)
  - RLEA: Transportation Communication Employees, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 55)
  - RLEA: Seafarers' International Union of North America, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 56)
  - RLEA: Canadian Affairs, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 57)
  - RLEA: Meetings, General, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 58)
  - RLEA: Miami Meeting of RLEA, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 59)
  - RLEA: Agendas, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 60)
  - RLEA: Reports of Counsel, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 61)
  - RLEA: Assessments, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 62)
  - RLEA: Application for Affiliation, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - RLEA: Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders' International Union, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - RLEA: Wages and Rules, General [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 141, Folder 3a)
  - RLEA: Wages and Rules, General [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 141, Folder 3b)
  - RLEA: Southern Rules Movement, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - RLEA: Chicago and Northwestern Rules Movement, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - RLEA: Butte, Anaconda, and Pacific Rules Movement, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - RLEA: Job Stabilization Movement on the MKT Railroad, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - RLEA: 1961 Wage and Rules Movement, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - RLEA: Radio-Telephone Equipment Communications, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - RLEA: 1962 Rules Movement, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - RLEA: Chicago and Illinois Midland Railway, Section 6 Notice, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - RLEA: Florida East Coast Railway, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - RLEA: Louisville and Nashville "No Injury" Reports, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - RLEA: 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 14)
  - RLEA: Changes in Discipline Policy and Procedures, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 15)
  - RLEA: Employment and Medical Examination Policy and Procedure, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 16)
  - RLEA: Compulsory Retirement, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 17)
  - RLEA: N and W's Railways Thrift Plan for Non-Union Employees, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 18)
  - RLEA: 1966 Wage Rules Movement, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 19)
  - RLEA: 1967 Wage and Rules Guaranteed Annual Wage [folder 1 of 2] (Box 141, Folder 20a)
  - RLEA: 1967 Wage and Rules Guaranteed Annual Wage [folder 2 of 2] (Box 141, Folder 20b)
  - RLEA: Health and Welfare, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 21)
  - RLEA: Travelers' Insurance Company, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 22)
  - RLEA: Operating Unions, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 23)
  - RLEA: Rules Committee, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 24)
  - RLEA: Carrier Strike Insurance Program, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 25)
  - RLEA: Automation, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 26)
  - RLEA: Union Shop, General, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 27)
  - RLEA: Union Dues, General, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 28)
  - RLEA: Diversification of Railroads, "Piggybacking", 1967 (Box 141, Folder 29)
  - RLEA: Permits on Railroad Property for Union Business, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 30)
  - RLEA: Railway Labor Building, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 31)
  - RLEA: Committees, General, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 32)
  - RLEA: Safety Committee, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 33)
  - RLEA: Committee to Study Railroad Mergers, Consolidation, etc., 1967 (Box 141, Folder 34)
  - RLEA: Keyserling Merger Study and related Subjects, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 35)
  - RLEA: Committee to Meet with Association of American Railroads, Railroad L-M Relations., 1967 (Box 141, Folder 36)
  - RLEA: Political Education Committee (PEC), 1967 (Box 141, Folder 37)
  - RLEA: Legislative Representatives, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 38)
  - RLEA: Passes, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 39)
  - RLEA: Personnel Records, General, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 40)
  - RLEA: Prospective Employees, General, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 41)
  - RLEA Department of Research and Education, Applications for Employment, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 42)
  - RLEA: Financial, General, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 43)
  - RLEA: Internal revenue Service Forms No. 990, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 44)
  - RLEA: Workmen's Compensation Tax, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 45)
  - RLEA: GPO Account No. 11256, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 46)
  - RLEA: Insurance, General, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 47)
  - RLEA: Postage Meter, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 48)
  - RLEA: Addressograph-Multigraph Corporation, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 49)
  - RLEA: Office Equipment, general, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 50)
  - RLEA: Office Furniture, General, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 51)
  - RLEA: Lawyers, General, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 52)
  - RLEA: Lawyers Bills [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 141, Folder 53a)
  - RLEA: Lawyers Bills [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 141, Folder 53b)
  - RLEA: Strikes, General [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 141, Folder 54a)
  - RLEA: Strikes, General [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 141, Folder 54b)
  - RLEA: Florida East Coast Railway Strike, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 55)
  - RLEA Shopcrafts Dispute (2/2), 1967 (Box 141, Folder 56)
  - RLEA: Shopcrafts Dispute (1/2) [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 141, Folder 57a)
  - RLEA: Shopcrafts Dispute (1/2) [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 141, Folder 57b)
  - Railroads: General, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 58)
  - Railroads: Illinois Central Railroad Industries, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Railroads: Commonwealth Edison-New York City - Coal Conveyor, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Railroads: Baltimore and Ohio Control of Reading Company, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads [folder 1 of 3], 1967 (Box 142, Folder 4a)
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads [folder 2 of 3], 1967 (Box 142, Folder 4b)
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads [folder 3 of 3], 1967 (Box 142, Folder 4c)
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads Highway User Charges, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Railroads: Association of Western Railroads, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Railroads: Carriers' Conference Committees - General, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Railroads: Eastern Governors' Conference on Railroad Problems, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Railroads: National Railway Labor Conference, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Railroads: Hospital Associations - General, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Railroads: Kansas City Southern, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Railroads: Missouri Pacific, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Railroads: Illinois Central Hospital Association, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - Railroads: Southern Pacific Hospital Department, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - Railroads: Western Pacific Hospital Association, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 15)
  - Railroads: Hospital Association Medicare, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 16)
  - Railroads: Tuition Aid Program - Union Pacific Railroad, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 17)
  - Railroads: Western and Atlantic Railroad (Proposed Lease by Southern Railroad), 1967 (Box 142, Folder 18)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 19)
  - Other Organizations: COPE, AFL-CIO, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 20)
  - Other Organizations: Free Trade Union News, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 21)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO - Minutes, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Legislative Action Bulletin, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Other Organizations: Legislative Council, AFL-CIO, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Other Organizations: Executive Council, AFL-CIO, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 25)
  - Other Organizations: Miscellaneous and General, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 26)
  - Other Organizations: Advertising Council, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 27)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 28)
  - Other Organizations: Pension Associations, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 29)
  - Other Organizations: Young Men's Christian Association, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 30)
  - Other Organizations: Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 31)
  - Other Organizations: Harvard University Trade Union Program, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 32)
  - Other Organizations: The Unions Retirement Foundation, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 33)
  - Other Organizations: United States Committee for the United Nations, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 34)
    Also includes papers for "United Nations - General"
  - Other Organizations: National Conference on International Economic and Social Development, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 35)